(Penny:)Hey. Isn't tomorrow
your usual laundry night?
(Sheldon:)The supermarket was out of
my regular fabric softener.
(Sheldon:)If this one under-
or over-softens,
(Sheldon:)I'll need time
to make things right.
(Penny:)That's thinking ahead.
(Sheldon:)The alternative would be
to think backwards.
(Sheldon:)That's just remembering.
(Penny:)So how's Amy?
(Sheldon:)Amy's changed.
(Sheldon:)I might have to let her go.
(Penny:)Oh, no. Why?
(Sheldon:)I thought she was
a highly evolved creature
(Sheldon:)of pure intellect, like me.
(Sheldon:)But recent events indicate that
(Sheldon:)she may be a slave
to her baser urges.
(Sheldon:)Like you.
(Penny:)Just going to
skip over that insult.
(Sheldon:)What insult?
(Penny:)Yeah. That's why
I'm going to skip over it.
(Penny:)Are you saying that Amy is...
(Penny:)oh, what's the
scientific word...
(Sheldon:)Forget science. She's horny.
(Penny:)Oh! Okay. Wow.